[{"instructions":"Let's define a new operation +<sub>6</sub>. This operation will give us a way of combining two of the numbers 0, 1, 2, 3, 4, 5 to get another one of them back. To perform +<sub>6</sub>, you start with the first number, and then add the second one to it. If the sum is smaller than 6, that's your result. If the sum is 6 or bigger, you subtract 6 to get your result. (That's why the operation is called +<sub>6</sub>.) <br /><br />For example, 3 +<sub>6</sub> 5 = 2, because 3 + 5 = 8, and 8 is bigger than 6, so we subtract 6, and 8 - 6 = 2. So 3 +<sub>6</sub> 5 = 2.<br /><br />Similarly, 1 +<sub>6</sub> 4 = 5, because 1 + 4 = 5, and 5 is less than 6 so we leave it alone.<br /><br />Click Continue when you're ready to move on.","rt":4175,"trial_type":"instructions","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":1,"time_elapsed":7148,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0"},{"instructions":"Do you see how +<sub>6</sub> works? By subtracting 6 every time we get above 5, we ensure that  when we  combine two numbers using +<sub>6</sub>, we only produce numbers between 0 and 5.<br /><br />Click Continue when you're ready to move on.","rt":14660,"trial_type":"instructions","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":2,"time_elapsed":21809,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0"},{"question":"Now try one on your own! What is 4 +<sub>6</sub> 5? <br /><br /> (Remember, to perform +<sub>6</sub>, you start with the first number, and then add the second one to it. If the sum is smaller than 6, that's your result. If the sum is 6 or bigger, you subtract 6 to get your result.)","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"3","response":"-1","response_history":["-1"],"rt":63302,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":3,"time_elapsed":85115,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.3-0"},{"feedback":"Sorry, that was incorrect. 4 +<sub>6</sub> 5 = 3 because 4 + 5 = 9 and 9 - 6 = 3.","rt":9082,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":4,"time_elapsed":94197,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.3-0"},{"question":"What is 3 +<sub>6</sub> 2? <br /><br /> (Remember, to perform +<sub>6</sub>, you start with the first number, and then add the second one to it. If the sum is smaller than 6, that's your result. If the sum is 6 or bigger, you subtract 6 to get your result.)","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"5","response":"5","response_history":["5"],"rt":28137,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":5,"time_elapsed":122334,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.3-0"},{"feedback":"Correct! 3 +<sub>6</sub> 2 = 5 because 3 + 2 = 5 and 5 is less than 6.","rt":5571,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":6,"time_elapsed":127905,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.3-0"},{"question":"What is 1 +<sub>6</sub> 5? <br /><br /> (Remember, to perform +<sub>6</sub>, you start with the first number, and then add the second one to it. If the sum is smaller than 6, that's your result. If the sum is 6 or bigger, you subtra ct 6 to  get your result.)","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"0","response":"0","response_history":["0"],"rt":11449,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":7,"time_elapsed":139355,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.3-0"},{"feedback":"Correct! 1 +<sub>6</sub> 5 = 0 because 1 + 5 = 6 and 6 - 6 = 0.","rt":1164,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":8,"time_elapsed":140519,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.3-0"},{"question":"What is 1 +<sub>6</sub> 1? <br /><br /> (Remember, to perform +<sub>6</sub>, you start with the first number, and then add the second one to it. If the sum is smaller than 6, that's your result. If the sum is 6 or bigger, you subtract 6 to get your result.)","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"2","response":"2","response_history":["2"],"rt":7576,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":9,"time_elapsed":148096,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.3-0"},{"feedback":"Correct! 1 + <sub>6</ sub> 1 = 2 because 1 + 1 = 2 and 2 is less than 6.","rt":1111,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":10,"time_elapsed":149207,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.3-0"},{"question":"What is 3 +<sub>6</sub> 0? <br /><br /> (Remember, to perform +<sub>6</sub>, you start with the first number, and then add the second one to it. If the sum is smaller than 6, that's your result. If the sum is 6 or bigger, you subtract 6 to get your result.)","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"3","response":"3","response_history":["3"],"rt":2919,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":11,"time_elapsed":152127,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.3-0"},{"feedback":"Correct! 3 +<sub>6</sub> 0 = 3 because 3 + 0 = 3 and 3 is less than 6.","rt":1182,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":12,"time_elapsed":153310,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.3-0"},{"question":"What is 4 +<sub>6</sub> 4? <br /><br /> (Remember, to perform +<sub>6</sub>, y ou start  with the first number, and then add the second one to it. If the sum is smaller than 6, that's your result. If the sum is 6 or bigger, you subtract 6 to get your result.)","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"2","response":"2","response_history":["2"],"rt":5185,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":13,"time_elapsed":158495,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.3-0"},{"feedback":"Correct! 4 +<sub>6</sub> 4 = 2 because 4 + 4 = 8 and 8 - 6 = 2.","rt":1143,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":14,"time_elapsed":159639,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.3-0"},{"question":"What is 1 +<sub>6</sub> 3? <br /><br /> (Remember, to perform +<sub>6</sub>, you start with the first number, and then add the second one to it. If the sum is smaller than 6, that's your result. If the sum is 6 or bigger, you subtract 6 to get your result.)","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"4","response":"4","response_history":[" 4"],"rt":4705,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":15,"time_elapsed":164344,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.3-0"},{"feedback":"Correct! 1 +<sub>6</sub> 3 = 4 because 1 + 3 = 4 and 4 is less than 6.","rt":922,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":16,"time_elapsed":165267,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.3-0"},{"question":"What is 4 +<sub>6</sub> 3? <br /><br /> (Remember, to perform +<sub>6</sub>, you start with the first number, and then add the second one to it. If the sum is smaller than 6, that's your result. If the sum is 6 or bigger, you subtract 6 to get your result.)","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"1","response":"1","response_history":["1"],"rt":4144,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":17,"time_elapsed":169411,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.3-0"},{"feedback":"Correct! 4 +<sub>6</sub> 3 = 1 because 4 + 3 = 7 and 7 - 6 = 1.","rt":711,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":18,"time_elapsed":170123,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.3-0"},{"question":"What is 0 +<sub>6</sub> 5? <br /><br /> (Remember, to perform +<sub>6</sub>, you start with the first number, and then add the second one to it. If the sum is smaller than 6, that's your result. If the sum is 6 or bigger, you subtract 6 to get your result.)","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"5","response":"5","response_history":["5"],"rt":3015,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":19,"time_elapsed":173139,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.3-0"},{"feedback":"Correct! 0 +<sub>6</sub> 5 = 5 because 0 + 5 = 5 and 5 is less than 6.","rt":763,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":20,"time_elapsed":173903,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.3-0"},{"question":"What is 2 +<sub>6</sub> 5? <br /><br /> (Remember, to perform +<sub>6</sub>, you start with the first number, and then add the second one to it. If the sum is smaller than 6, that's your result. If the sum is 6  or bigg er, you subtract 6 to get your result.)","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"1","response":"1","response_history":["1"],"rt":2718,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":21,"time_elapsed":176621,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.3-0"},{"feedback":"Correct! 2 +<sub>6</sub> 5 = 1 because 2 + 5 = 7 and 7 - 6 = 1.","rt":1086,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":22,"time_elapsed":177708,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.3-0"},{"instructions":"Now we're going to discuss a couple special properties of this new operation, +<sub>6</sub> that we've learned. First, notice that the number 0 behaves in a special way under +<sub>6</sub>. Whenever we combine 0 with anything else, we get that same thing back. We'll say that 0 is the <i>identity</i> under +<sub>6</sub>, because when you combine it with something it gives you that identical thing back.","rt":12576,"trial_type":"instructions","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":23,"time_elapsed":190286,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0"},{"instructions":"Now that we know 0 is the identity under +<sub>6</sub>, we're going to make a new definition. We'll say that the <i>inverse</i> of a number is the element that you combine with it to produce the identity. For example, 5 +<sub>6</sub> 1 = 0, so we say 1 is the inverse of 5 under +<sub>6</sub>, (remember 0 is the identity under +<sub>6</sub>). Similarly, 3 is its own inverse under +<sub>6</sub>, because 3 +<sub>6</sub> 3 = 0.","rt":67370,"trial_type":"instructions","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":24,"time_elapsed":257657,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0"},{"question":"Now you try! What is the inverse of 4 under +<sub>6</sub>? <br /><br /> (Remember, the inverse of an element is the thing which you combine with it to produce the identity.)","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"2","response":"2","response_history":["2"],"rt":9780,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":25,"time_elapsed":267439,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.7-0"},{"feedback":"Correct! The inverse of 4 under +<sub>6</sub> is 2 because 4 +<sub>6</sub> 2 = 0, and 0 is the identity under +<sub>6</sub>.","rt":4546,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":26,"time_elapsed":271986,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.7-0"},{"question":"What is the inverse of 1 under +<sub>6</sub>? <br /><br /> (Remember, the inverse of an element is the thing which you combine with it to produce the identity.)","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"5","response":"5","response_history":["5"],"rt":3227,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":27,"time_elapsed":275214,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.7-0"},{"feedback":"Correct! The inverse of 1 under +<sub>6</sub> is 5 because 1 +<sub>6</sub> 5 = 0, and 0 is the identity under +<sub>6</sub>.","rt":1001,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":28,"time_elapsed":276216,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.7-0"},{"question":"What is  the inverse of 3 under +<sub>6</sub>? <br /><br /> (Remember, the inverse of an element is the thing which you combine with it to produce the identity.)","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"3","response":"3","response_history":["3"],"rt":2369,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":29,"time_elapsed":278585,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.7-0"},{"feedback":"Correct! The inverse of 3 under +<sub>6</sub> is 3 because 3 +<sub>6</sub> 3 = 0, and 0 is the identity under +<sub>6</sub>.","rt":1039,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":30,"time_elapsed":279625,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.7-0"},{"question":"What is the inverse of 2 under +<sub>6</sub>? <br /><br /> (Remember, the inverse of an element is the thing which you combine with it to produce the identity.)","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"4","response":"4","response_history":["4"],"rt":2293,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":31,"time_elapsed":281919,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.7-0"},{"feedback":"Correct! The inverse of 2 under +<sub>6</sub> is 4 because 2 +<sub>6</sub> 4 = 0, and 0 is the identity under +<sub>6</sub>.","rt":650,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":32,"time_elapsed":282569,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.7-0"},{"question":"What is the inverse of 0 under +<sub>6</sub>? <br /><br /> (Remember, the inverse of an element is the thing which you combine with it to produce the identity.)","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"0","response":"6","response_history":["6"],"rt":3252,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":33,"time_elapsed":285821,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.7-0"},{"feedback":"Sorry, that was incorrect. The inverse of 0 under +<sub>6</sub> is 0 because 0 +<sub>6</sub> 0 = 0, and 0 is the identity under +<sub>6</sub>.","rt":5706,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":34,"time_elapsed":291528,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.7-0"},{"instructions":"It is also possible to successively apply +<sub>6</sub>, and the operation can simply be performed starting with the left-most pair. For example, 2 +<sub>6</sub> 3 +<sub>6</sub> 4 = 5 +<sub>6</sub> 4 = 3.","rt":12015,"trial_type":"instructions","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":35,"time_elapsed":303544,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0"},{"instructions":"We have one last definition to learn today, using the successive operations we just learned. Let's start with an example. Under our operation +<sub>6</sub> we can make every other number using just 1: 2 = 1 +<sub>6</sub> 1, 3 = 1 +<sub>6</sub> 1 +<sub>6</sub> 1, 4 = 1 +<sub>6</sub> 1 +<sub>6</sub> 1 +<sub>6</sub> 1, 5 = 1 +<sub>6</sub> 1 +<sub>6</sub> 1 +<sub>6</sub> 1 +<sub>6</sub> 1, and 0 = 1 +<sub>6</sub> 1 +<sub>6</sub> 1 +<sub>6</sub> 1 +<sub>6</sub> 1 +<sub>6</sub> 1. Because 1 can make every other element under +<sub>6</sub>, we say that 1 is a <i>generator</i> under +<sub>6< /sub>. < br /><br /> However, 2 is not a generator under +<sub>6</sub>, because 4 = 2 +<sub>6</sub> 2, and 0 = 2 +<sub>6</sub> 2 +<sub>6</sub> 2, but there is no way to make 1, 3, or 5 using just 2.","rt":1625,"trial_type":"instructions","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":36,"time_elapsed":305170,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0"},{"question":"Now you try! Is 3 a generator under +<sub>6</sub>? <br /><br /> (Remember, a generator is an element which can make every other element.)","response_type":"multi","response_choices":["Yes","No"],"correct_response":"No","response":"No","response_history":["No"],"rt":9586,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":37,"time_elapsed":314757,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.10-0"},{"feedback":"Correct! 3 is not a generator under +<sub>6</sub>, because 3 = 3, 0 = 3 +<sub>6</sub> 3, but there is no way to make 1, 2, 4, or 5 using just 3.","rt":8013,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":38,"time_elapsed":322770,"internal_chunk_id":"0 -0.10-0"},{"question":"Is 5 a generator under +<sub>6</sub>? <br /><br /> (Remember, a generator is an element which can make every other element.)","response_type":"multi","response_choices":["Yes","No"],"correct_response":"Yes","response":"Yes","response_history":["Yes"],"rt":3590,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":39,"time_elapsed":326360,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.10-0"},{"feedback":"Correct! 5 is a generator under +<sub>6</sub>, because 5 = 5, 4 = 5 +<sub>6</sub> 5, 3 = 5 +<sub>6</sub> 5 +<sub>6</sub> 5, 2 = 5 +<sub>6</sub> 5 +<sub>6</sub> 5 +<sub>6</sub> 5, 1 = 5 +<sub>6</sub> 5 +<sub>6</sub> 5 +<sub>6</sub> 5 +<sub>6</sub> 5, and 0 = 5 +<sub>6</sub> 5 +<sub>6</sub> 5 +<sub>6</sub> 5 +<sub>6</sub> 5 +<sub>6</sub> 5, so you can make all of the numbers under +<sub>6</sub> using 5","rt":1309,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":40,"time_elapsed":327670,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.10-0"},{"question":"Is 4 a generator under +<sub >6</sub> ? <br /><br /> (Remember, a generator is an element which can make every other element.)","response_type":"multi","response_choices":["Yes","No"],"correct_response":"No","response":"No","response_history":["No"],"rt":2577,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":41,"time_elapsed":330247,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.10-0"},{"feedback":"Correct! 4 is not a generator under +<sub>6</sub>, because 4 = 4, 2 = 4 +<sub>6</sub> 4, and 0 = 4 +<sub>6</sub> 4 +<sub>6</sub> 4, but there is no way to make 1, 3, or 5 using just 4.","rt":1096,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":42,"time_elapsed":331344,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.10-0"},{"question":"Is 0 a generator under +<sub>6</sub>? <br /><br /> (Remember, a generator is an element which can make every other element.)","response_type":"multi","response_choices":["Yes","No"],"correct_response":"No","response":"Yes","response_history":["Yes"],"rt":2821,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":43,"time_elapsed":334166,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.10-0"},{"feedback":"Sorry, that's incorrect. 0 is not a generator under +<sub>6</sub>, because 0 = 0, but there is no way to make 1, 2, 3, 4, or 5 using just 0.","rt":1051,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":44,"time_elapsed":335217,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.10-0"},{"instructions":"Now we are going to ask you some questions about a new operation, +<sub>9</sub>, on the numbers 0, 1, 2, 3, 4, 5, 6, 7, 8. It works exactly like +<sub>6</sub>, except now after adding the two numbers you subtract 9 if your result is 9 or greater. <br /><br />Do you see how +<sub>9</sub> works just like +<sub>6</sub>? By subtracting 9 every time we get above 8, we ensure that when we combine two numbers using +<sub>9</sub>, we only produce numbers between 0 and 8.<br /><br />We'll give you one practice question with feedback to make sure you understand the new operation. After that, try to complete the remaining questions  as accu rately as possible.","rt":31799,"trial_type":"instructions","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":45,"time_elapsed":367016,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0"},{"question":"Practice: What is 5 +<sub>9</sub> 5?","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"1","response":"1","response_history":["1"],"rt":4911,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":46,"time_elapsed":371928,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.12-0"},{"feedback":"Correct! 5 +<sub>9</sub> 5 = 1 because 5 + 5 = 10 and 10 - 9 = 1.","rt":1017,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":47,"time_elapsed":372946,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.12-0"},{"question":"What is 3 +<sub>9</sub> 3?","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"6","response":"6","response_history":["6"],"rt":3882,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":48,"time_elapsed":376828,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.12-0"},{"question":"What is 7 +<sub>9</sub> 4?","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"2","response":"2","response_history":["2"],"rt":6253,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":49,"time_elapsed":383082,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.12-0"},{"question":"What is 1 +<sub>9</sub> 8?","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"0","response":"0","response_history":["0"],"rt":5812,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":50,"time_elapsed":388895,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.12-0"},{"question":"What is 5 +<sub>9</sub> 4?","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"0","response":"0","response_history":["0"],"rt":6256,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":51,"time_elapsed":395151,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.12-0"},{"question":"What is 6 +<sub>9</sub> 6?","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"3","response":"3","response_history":["3"],"rt":7804,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":52,"time_elapsed":402955,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.12-0"},{"question":"What is 4 +<sub>9</sub> 1? Please explain in words how you got your answer.","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"","response":"5. You add 4 + 1 which = 5. 5 is less than 9 so that's the answer.","response_history":["4. You add 4 + 1 which ","5. You add 4 + 1 which = 5. 5 is less than 9 so thats the answer.","5. You add 4 + 1 which = 5. 5 is less than 9 so that's the answer."],"rt":39554,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":53,"time_elapsed":442509,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.12-0"},{"question":"What is 8 +<sub>9</sub> 4? Please explain in words how you got your answer.","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"","response":"3. 8+4 is 12. 12 is greater than 9 so you subtract 9 from 12 which is 3.","response_history":["3/","3. 8+4 is 12. 12 is greater than 9 so you subrea","3. 8+4 is 12. 12 is greater than 9 so you subre","3. 8+4 is 12. 12 is greater than 9  so you  subrt","3. 8+4 is 12. 12 is greater than 9 so you subr","3. 8+4 is 12. 12 is greater than 9 so you subtract 9 from 12 which is 3./","3. 8+4 is 12. 12 is greater than 9 so you subtract 9 from 12 which is 3."],"rt":36142,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":54,"time_elapsed":478652,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.12-0"},{"question":"What is the identity under +<sub>9</sub>? Please explain in words how you got your answer.","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"0","response":"I think the Identity is 9. Because that makes it 0","response_history":["9 because thats how many","9? I hon","9? ","9?","9","the identi","I think the i","I think the Identir","I think the Identity is 0","I think the Identity is 9. Because thats the highest nnumb","I think the Identity is 9. Because thats ","I think the Identity is 9. Because thats","I think the Identity is 9. Because that makes it 0"],"rt":53654,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":55,"time_elapsed":532307,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.12-0"},{"question":"What is the inverse of 5 under +<sub>9</sub>?","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"4","response":"4","response_history":["4"],"rt":6180,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":56,"time_elapsed":538487,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.12-0"},{"question":"What is the inverse of 2 under +<sub>9</sub>?","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"7","response":"7","response_history":["7"],"rt":3707,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":57,"time_elapsed":542195,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.12-0"},{"question":"What is the inverse of 0 under +<sub>9</sub>?","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"0","response":"9","response_history":["9"],"rt":5108,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":58,"time_elapsed":547304,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.12-0"},{"question":"What is the inverse of 3 und er +<sub >9</sub>? Please explain in words how you got your answer.","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"","response":"6. Because you need 6 more to get to 9 from 3.","response_history":["6. Because you need 6 more to gewt","6. Because you need 6 more to gew","6. Because you need 6 more to get to 9 from 3."],"rt":18769,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":59,"time_elapsed":566074,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.12-0"},{"question":"Is 2 a generator under +<sub>9</sub>? Please explain in words how you got your answer.","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"","response":"no because it doesn't cause it to go over","response_history":["no. It doesn't ","no. It","no. I","no. ","no.","no because it doesnt ","no because it doesnt","no because it doesn't csu","no because it doesn't cs","no because it doesn't cu","no because it doesn't cause it to go over"],"rt":31982,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":60,"time_elapsed":598056,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.12-0"},{"question":"Is 3 a generator under +<sub>9</sub>? Please explain in words how you got your answer.","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"","response":"I dont know. I think it is.","response_history":["yes because its m","yes because its less than half","I dont know. I think it is."],"rt":40254,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":61,"time_elapsed":638311,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.12-0"},{"question":"Is 5 a generator under +<sub>9</sub>? Please explain in words how you got your answer.","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"","response":"Yes because its greater than half","response_history":["Yes because its greater than half"],"rt":10503,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":62,"time_elapsed":648816,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.12-0"},{"question":"Is 6 a generator under +<sub>9</sub>? Please explain in words how you got you r answer .","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"","response":"yes because its greater than half","response_history":["yes because its greater than half"],"rt":7910,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":63,"time_elapsed":656727,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.12-0"},{"instructions":"Now we'd like to ask you some questions about +<sub>n</sub>, where n could be any postive counting number. For example, n could be 3, or n could be any other counting number you can think of. If you need to write the operation, you can use +_n, and your answers can include n to stand in for the arbitrary value if necessary.","rt":4015,"trial_type":"instructions","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":64,"time_elapsed":660743,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0"},{"question":"What is the formula for the inverse of 1 under +<sub>n</sub>?","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"n-1","response":"1+n","response_history":["1+2","1+n"],"rt":14591,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":65,"time_elapsed":675334,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.14-0"},{"question":"What is the formula for the inverse of an element x under +<sub>n</sub>? Please explain in words how you got your answer.","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"n-x","response":"I honestly have no clue this is getting a little too complicated for me","response_history":["I honestly have no clue this is getting a,","I honestly have no clue this is getting a little too complicated for me"],"rt":18920,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":66,"time_elapsed":694255,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.14-0"},{"question":"Is there a pattern to which elements are generators? How can you know if an element x is a generator under +<sub>n</sub> without seeing whether it can make all the elements?.","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"","response":"I think there is a definite pattern, im just not picking  up on i t.","response_history":["OI","O","I think there is a definite patter,","I think there is a definite pattern, im just not picking uo on","I think there is a definite pattern, im just not picking uo o","I think there is a definite pattern, im just not picking uo ","I think there is a definite pattern, im just not picking uo","I think there is a definite pattern, im just not picking up on it."],"rt":21449,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":67,"time_elapsed":715704,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.14-0"},{"question":"True or false: If x is an odd number, it must be a generator under +<sub>n</sub>.","response_type":"multi","response_choices":["True","False"],"correct_response":"False","response":"False","response_history":["False"],"rt":4988,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":68,"time_elapsed":720692,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.14-0"},{"question":"True or false: If x is an even number, it must not be a generator under +<sub>n</sub>.","response_type":"multi","response_choices":["True","False"],"correct_response":"False","response":"True","response_history":["True"],"rt":3311,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":69,"time_elapsed":724004,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.14-0"},{"question":"True or false: If x is not a generator under +<sub>n</sub>, x must be a divisor of n, that is, x must divide n evenly, with no remainder.","response_type":"multi","response_choices":["True","False"],"correct_response":"False","response":"True","response_history":["True"],"rt":2500,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":70,"time_elapsed":726505,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.14-0"},{"question":"True or false: If x is not a generator under +<sub>n</sub>, x must be a multiple of a divisor of n. Please explain in words why your answer is correct.","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"True","response":"true? I don't know anymore","response_history":["false","fals","fal","fa","f"," true? I  dont","true? I don't know anymore"],"rt":30021,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":71,"time_elapsed":756526,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.14-0"},{"question":"If an element x is a generator under +<sub>n</sub>, is its inverse a generator under +<sub>n</sub> always, sometimes, or never?","response_type":"multi","response_choices":["Always","Sometimes","Never"],"correct_response":"Always","response":"Sometimes","response_history":["Sometimes"],"rt":5607,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":72,"time_elapsed":762134,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.14-0"},{"question":"if an element x is a generator under +<sub>n</sub>, is x +<sub>n</sub> x a generator under +<sub>n</sub> always, sometimes, or never? Please explain in words why your answer is correct.","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"sometimes","response":"I have absolutely no clue at all","response_history":["I have no clue wht","I have no clue whether its a gen e","I ha ve no clue whether its a gen","I have no clue whether its a generator","I have no c","I have no ","I have no","I have n","I have absolutely no clue at all.","I have absolutely no clue at all"],"rt":38374,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":73,"time_elapsed":800508,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.14-0"},{"question":"If an element x is not a generator under +<sub>n</sub>, is x +<sub>n</sub> x a generator under +<sub>n</sub> always, sometimes, or never?","response_type":"multi","response_choices":["Always","Sometimes","Never"],"correct_response":"Never","response":"Never","response_history":["Never"],"rt":3353,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":74,"time_elapsed":803861,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.14-0"},{"instructions":"We would like to ask you some questions about your background. Please press Continue to continue.","rt":2544,"trial_type":"instructions","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":75,"time_elapsed":806406,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.1 5-0"},{"question":"What is your age?","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"","response":"20","response_history":["20"],"rt":2316,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":76,"time_elapsed":808723,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.15-0"},{"question":"What is your level of education?","response_type":"multi","response_choices":["Did not graduate high school","High school diploma","Some college, no degree","Associates Degree","Bachelors Degree","Some graduate school, no degree","Masters Degree","Doctorate, M.D., etc."],"correct_response":"","response":"High school diploma","response_history":["High school diploma"],"rt":3357,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":77,"time_elapsed":812081,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.15-0"},{"question":"What is the most advanced math class you've completed? If you have multiple classes and you're not sure which one is most advanced, please list them.","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"","response":"algebra 1. I'm horrible at math.","response_history":["algebra 1. Im horrible at math,","algebra 1. Im horrible at math.","algebra 1. I'm horrible at math."],"rt":23013,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":78,"time_elapsed":835096,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.15-0"},{"question":"How familiar are you with the concept of modular arithmetic?","response_type":"multi","response_choices":["1 - never heard of it","2 - heard of it but didn't know what it was","3 - seen it used or explained","4 - used it but not often or recently","5 - used it, remember and understand it"],"correct_response":"1","response":"1 - never heard of it","response_history":["1 - never heard of it"],"rt":4984,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":79,"time_elapsed":840080,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.15-0"},{"question":"How familiar are you with the concept of a mathematical group?","response_type":"multi","response_choices":["1 - never hea rd of it ","2 - heard of it but didn't know what it was","3 - seen it used or explained","4 - used it but not often or recently","5 - used it, remember and understand it"],"correct_response":"1","response":"2 - heard of it but didn't know what it was","response_history":["2 - heard of it but didn't know what it was","3 - seen it used or explained","2 - heard of it but didn't know what it was"],"rt":7840,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":80,"time_elapsed":847920,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.15-0"},{"question":"Do you feel you learned something from this HIT?","response_type":"multi","response_choices":["1 - not at all","2 - somewhat","3 - definitely"],"correct_response":"1","response":"2 - somewhat","response_history":["2 - somewhat"],"rt":3694,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":81,"time_elapsed":851615,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.15-0"},{"question":"Do you feel you understood the concepts in this HIT?","response_type":"multi","response_choices":["1 - not at all","2 - somewhat","3 - definitely"],"correct_response":"1","response":"2 - somewhat","response_history":["2 - somewhat"],"rt":3292,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":82,"time_elapsed":854908,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.15-0"},{"question":"Did you enjoy this HIT?","response_type":"multi","response_choices":["1 - not at all","2 - somewhat","3 - definitely"],"correct_response":"1","response":"3 - definitely","response_history":["2 - somewhat","3 - definitely"],"rt":4240,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":83,"time_elapsed":859148,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.15-0"},{"question":"What is your gender?","response_type":"multi","response_choices":["Female","Male","Other"],"correct_response":"","response":"Male","response_history":["Male"],"rt":1804,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":84,"time_elapsed":860954,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.15-0"},{"question":"What is/are your native language(s)? (The languag es spoke n in your household when you were a child.)","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"","response":"English","response_history":["English"],"rt":4858,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":85,"time_elapsed":865813,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.15-0"},{"question":"Did you use pen and paper at any point on this HIT?","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"","response":"nope","response_history":["nope"],"rt":3388,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":86,"time_elapsed":869201,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.15-0"},{"question":"Do you have any comments on this HIT?","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"","response":"Thanks a lot for the HIT. This was really interesting and entertaining. I started getting confused after a while though, I'm not that good at math and didn't know this was going to be a math HIT so it kind of caught me off guard. I hope my answers are still b eneficia l to you even though I didn't know the answers for the last couple pages. Thanks again, great survey!","response_history":["Thanks a lot fdo","Thanks a lot fd","Thanks a lot for the HIT,.","Thanks a lot for the HIT,","Thanks a lot for the HIT/.","Thanks a lot for the HIT/","Thanks a lot for the HIT. This was really inter","Thanks a lot for the HIT. This was really interesting and entertaining. I stare","Thanks a lot for the HIT. This was really interesting and entertaining. I started getting conb","Thanks a lot for the HIT. This was really interesting and entertaining. I started getting confused after a while though, I'm not that good at math and didn't know this was going to be a mt","Thanks a lot for the HIT. This was really interesting and entertaining. I started getting confused after a while though, I'm not that good at math and didn't know this was going to be a math h","Thanks a lot for the HIT. This was really interesting and entertaining. I started getting confused  after a  while though, I'm not that good at math and didn't know this was going to be a math HIT so it kind of caught me off guya","Thanks a lot for the HIT. This was really interesting and entertaining. I started getting confused after a while though, I'm not that good at math and didn't know this was going to be a math HIT so it kind of caught me off guy","Thanks a lot for the HIT. This was really interesting and entertaining. I started getting confused after a while though, I'm not that good at math and didn't know this was going to be a math HIT so it kind of caught me off guard. I hope my answers atr","Thanks a lot for the HIT. This was really interesting and entertaining. I started getting confused after a while though, I'm not that good at math and didn't know this was going to be a math HIT so it kind of caught me off guard. I hope my answers at","Thanks a lot for the HIT. This was really interesting and entertaining. I started getting confused after a while though, I'm not t hat good  at math and didn't know this was going to be a math HIT so it kind of caught me off guard. I hope my answers are still beneficial to you evewn ","Thanks a lot for the HIT. This was really interesting and entertaining. I started getting confused after a while though, I'm not that good at math and didn't know this was going to be a math HIT so it kind of caught me off guard. I hope my answers are still beneficial to you evewn","Thanks a lot for the HIT. This was really interesting and entertaining. I started getting confused after a while though, I'm not that good at math and didn't know this was going to be a math HIT so it kind of caught me off guard. I hope my answers are still beneficial to you evew","Thanks a lot for the HIT. This was really interesting and entertaining. I started getting confused after a while though, I'm not that good at math and didn't know this was going to be a math HIT so it kind of caught me off guard. I hope my answers are still beneficial to you  even th iou","Thanks a lot for the HIT. This was really interesting and entertaining. I started getting confused after a while though, I'm not that good at math and didn't know this was going to be a math HIT so it kind of caught me off guard. I hope my answers are still beneficial to you even thio","Thanks a lot for the HIT. This was really interesting and entertaining. I started getting confused after a while though, I'm not that good at math and didn't know this was going to be a math HIT so it kind of caught me off guard. I hope my answers are still beneficial to you even thi","Thanks a lot for the HIT. This was really interesting and entertaining. I started getting confused after a while though, I'm not that good at math and didn't know this was going to be a math HIT so it kind of caught me off guard. I hope my answers are still beneficial to you even though I didn't know what ha","Thanks a lot for the HIT. This was really interesting and entertaining. I started getting confus ed after  a while though, I'm not that good at math and didn't know this was going to be a math HIT so it kind of caught me off guard. I hope my answers are still beneficial to you even though I didn't know what h","Thanks a lot for the HIT. This was really interesting and entertaining. I started getting confused after a while though, I'm not that good at math and didn't know this was going to be a math HIT so it kind of caught me off guard. I hope my answers are still beneficial to you even though I didn't know what was going on for ","Thanks a lot for the HIT. This was really interesting and entertaining. I started getting confused after a while though, I'm not that good at math and didn't know this was going to be a math HIT so it kind of caught me off guard. I hope my answers are still beneficial to you even though I didn't know the answers for the last coupld ","Thanks a lot for the HIT. This was really interesting and entertaining. I started getting confused after a while thoug h, I'm n ot that good at math and didn't know this was going to be a math HIT so it kind of caught me off guard. I hope my answers are still beneficial to you even though I didn't know the answers for the last coupld","Thanks a lot for the HIT. This was really interesting and entertaining. I started getting confused after a while though, I'm not that good at math and didn't know this was going to be a math HIT so it kind of caught me off guard. I hope my answers are still beneficial to you even though I didn't know the answers for the last couple pages. Thanks agauin","Thanks a lot for the HIT. This was really interesting and entertaining. I started getting confused after a while though, I'm not that good at math and didn't know this was going to be a math HIT so it kind of caught me off guard. I hope my answers are still beneficial to you even though I didn't know the answers for the last couple pages. Thanks agaui","Thanks a lot for the HIT. This was really interesting and entertai ning. I  started getting confused after a while though, I'm not that good at math and didn't know this was going to be a math HIT so it kind of caught me off guard. I hope my answers are still beneficial to you even though I didn't know the answers for the last couple pages. Thanks agau","Thanks a lot for the HIT. This was really interesting and entertaining. I started getting confused after a while though, I'm not that good at math and didn't know this was going to be a math HIT so it kind of caught me off guard. I hope my answers are still beneficial to you even though I didn't know the answers for the last couple pages. Thanks again, great survey!"],"rt":80803,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":87,"time_elapsed":950005,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.15-0"}]